Christmas Belle is a drama, romance, tv movie film directed by Alex Wright.
With her California hometown in the rearview mirror, Belle heads north
on business to catalog the sale of a large mansion.
While the job is a dream, the client, Hunter Lowell, is not.
But, as the two spend more time together, his icy demeanor begins to melt.
Although their relationship is budding, Belle’s long-time suitor, Tony, arrives,
sending mixed signals to Hunter while adding chaos to the holiday season.
Isabella Everhart, played by Haylie Duff.
Hunter Lowell, played by Nicholas Gonzalez.
Tony, played by Mark Famiglietti.
Rex Everhart, played by C. Thomas Howell.
Angie, played by Sheree J. Wilson.
Burny, played by Jerry Hauck.
Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas is a 1997 direct-to-video animated Christmas musical fantasy film produced by Walt Disney
Television Animation and Disneytoon Studios, as a sequel to Disney's 1991 animated feature film Beauty and the Beast.
The film was released by Walt Disney Home Video on November 11, 1997.
While a frame story is set after the events of the original film, the main narrative is
a flashback recounting Belle and the Beast's first Christmas together.
The film sold 7.6 million VHS tapes in 1997.
The tone is emotional.